<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:8107/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:8107/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-05-19T20:26:31+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:8107/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Autumn</title><subtitle>Autumn is a minimalist Jekyll theme made by &lt;a href=&quot;https://connorbaer.co/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot;&gt;Connor&lt;/a&gt;.</subtitle><author><name>Connor Bär</name><email>hello@connorbaer.co</email></author><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Autumn Romance</title><link href="http://localhost:8107/autumn-romance/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Autumn Romance" /><published>2019-01-09T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2019-01-09T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:8107/autumn-romance</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:8107/autumn-romance/">&lt;p&gt;You’re sitting in your apartment, on your freshly cleaned sheets, with pumpkin candles burning, and an old book that’s new to you in your hands. It’s just warm enough that you can leave the window open, and as you read, a breeze of crisp air flows through, and pushes the pages forward. You’re wearing warm socks and a big sweater, and you’re waiting for something to be done in the oven, something you’ve made for someone to come share with you — that someone with whom you’d like to analogize your relationship to blooming like spring, but you know it’s more accurately that you’re settling into each other’s warmth you embrace this change, just like you do autumn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Taken from &lt;a href=&quot;https://thoughtcatalog.com/chelsea-fagan/2013/09/6-one-paragraph-stories-about-autumn-that-will-make-you-cry-pumpkin-spice-tears/&quot;&gt;Thought Catalog&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href=&quot;https://thoughtcatalog.com/chelsea-fagan/&quot;&gt;Chelsea Fagan&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://thoughtcatalog.com/brianna-wiest/&quot;&gt;Brianna Wiest&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Connor Bär</name><email>hello@connorbaer.co</email></author><summary type="html">You’re sitting in your apartment, on your freshly cleaned sheets, with pumpkin candles burning, and an old book that’s new to you in your hands. It’s just warm enough that you can leave the window open, and as you read, a breeze of crisp air flows through, and pushes the pages forward. You’re wearing warm socks and a big sweater, and you’re waiting for something to be done in the oven, something you’ve made for someone to come share with you — that someone with whom you’d like to analogize your relationship to blooming like spring, but you know it’s more accurately that you’re settling into each other’s warmth you embrace this change, just like you do autumn. Taken from Thought Catalog by Chelsea Fagan and Brianna Wiest.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:8107/true" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:8107/true" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Japanese Maple</title><link href="http://localhost:8107/japanese-maple/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Japanese Maple" /><published>2019-01-08T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2019-01-08T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:8107/japanese-maple</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:8107/japanese-maple/">&lt;p&gt;Your death, near now, is of an easy sort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So slow a fading out brings no real pain.&lt;br /&gt;
Breath growing short&lt;br /&gt;
Is just uncomfortable. You feel the drain&lt;br /&gt;
Of energy, but thought and sight remain:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enhanced, in fact. When did you ever see&lt;br /&gt;
So much sweet beauty as when fine rain falls&lt;br /&gt;
On that small tree&lt;br /&gt;
And saturates your brick back garden walls,&lt;br /&gt;
So many Amber Rooms and mirror halls?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ever more lavish as the dusk descends&lt;br /&gt;
This glistening illuminates the air.&lt;br /&gt;
It never ends.&lt;br /&gt;
Whenever the rain comes it will be there,&lt;br /&gt;
Beyond my time, but now I take my share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My daughter’s choice, the maple tree is new.&lt;br /&gt;
Come autumn and its leaves will turn to flame.&lt;br /&gt;
What I must do&lt;br /&gt;
Is live to see that. That will end the game&lt;br /&gt;
For me, though life continues all the same:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Filling the double doors to bathe my eyes,&lt;br /&gt;
A final flood of colours will live on&lt;br /&gt;
As my mind dies,&lt;br /&gt;
Burned by my vision of a world that shone&lt;br /&gt;
So brightly at the last, and then was gone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.panmacmillan.com/authors/clive-james/sentenced-to-life/9781447284055&quot;&gt;Sentenced to Life&lt;/a&gt; by Clive James.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Connor Bär</name><email>hello@connorbaer.co</email></author><summary type="html">Your death, near now, is of an easy sort. So slow a fading out brings no real pain. Breath growing short Is just uncomfortable. You feel the drain Of energy, but thought and sight remain: Enhanced, in fact. When did you ever see So much sweet beauty as when fine rain falls On that small tree And saturates your brick back garden walls, So many Amber Rooms and mirror halls? Ever more lavish as the dusk descends This glistening illuminates the air. It never ends. Whenever the rain comes it will be there, Beyond my time, but now I take my share. My daughter’s choice, the maple tree is new. Come autumn and its leaves will turn to flame. What I must do Is live to see that. That will end the game For me, though life continues all the same: Filling the double doors to bathe my eyes, A final flood of colours will live on As my mind dies, Burned by my vision of a world that shone So brightly at the last, and then was gone. From Sentenced to Life by Clive James.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:8107/true" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:8107/true" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">October</title><link href="http://localhost:8107/october/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="October" /><published>2019-01-07T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2019-01-07T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:8107/october</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:8107/october/">&lt;p&gt;The green elm with the one great bough of gold&lt;br /&gt;
Lets leaves into the grass slip, one by one, –&lt;br /&gt;
The short hill grass, the mushrooms small milk-white,&lt;br /&gt;
Harebell and scabious and tormentil,&lt;br /&gt;
That blackberry and gorse, in dew and sun,&lt;br /&gt;
Bow down to; and the wind travels too light&lt;br /&gt;
To shake the fallen birch leaves from the fern;&lt;br /&gt;
The gossamers wander at their own will.&lt;br /&gt;
At heavier steps than birds’ the squirrels scold.&lt;br /&gt;
The rich scene has grown fresh again and new&lt;br /&gt;
As Spring and to the touch is not more cool&lt;br /&gt;
Than it is warm to the gaze; and now I might&lt;br /&gt;
As happy be as earth is beautiful,&lt;br /&gt;
Were I some other or with earth could turn&lt;br /&gt;
In alternation of violet and rose,&lt;br /&gt;
Harebell and snowdrop, at their season due,&lt;br /&gt;
And gorse that has no time not to be gay.&lt;br /&gt;
But if this be not happiness, – who knows?&lt;br /&gt;
Some day I shall think this a happy day,&lt;br /&gt;
And this mood by the name of melancholy&lt;br /&gt;
Shall no more blackened and obscured be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;By  Edward Thomas&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Connor Bär</name><email>hello@connorbaer.co</email></author><summary type="html">The green elm with the one great bough of gold Lets leaves into the grass slip, one by one, – The short hill grass, the mushrooms small milk-white, Harebell and scabious and tormentil, That blackberry and gorse, in dew and sun, Bow down to; and the wind travels too light To shake the fallen birch leaves from the fern; The gossamers wander at their own will. At heavier steps than birds’ the squirrels scold. The rich scene has grown fresh again and new As Spring and to the touch is not more cool Than it is warm to the gaze; and now I might As happy be as earth is beautiful, Were I some other or with earth could turn In alternation of violet and rose, Harebell and snowdrop, at their season due, And gorse that has no time not to be gay. But if this be not happiness, – who knows? Some day I shall think this a happy day, And this mood by the name of melancholy Shall no more blackened and obscured be. By Edward Thomas</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:8107/true" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:8107/true" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>